Renaissance Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- France (Box 32)
  - Cities (Box 35)
    - Paris (Box 43)
      - Plans (Box 43)
        - Turgot, 1734-39 (Box 43)
      - General Views (Box 43–44)
        - Various (Box 44)
        - Ile De La Cite (Box 44)
        - Ile S. Louis (Box 44)
        - Streets (Box 44)
      - Bridges (Box 44)
      - Cemeteries (Box 44)
      - Chateaux (Box 44)
        - Chateau de Bagatelle (Box 44)
        - Chateau de Madrid (Box 44)
      - Churches (Box 44)
        - Assumption (Box 44)
        - Invalides Church (Box 44)
        - Pere de la Charite (Box 44)
        - Minimes (Box 44)
        - Notre Dame (Box 44)
        - Notre Dame Des Victoires (Box 44)
        - Oratory Church (Box 44)
        - Pantheon (Box 44)
        - Sacre Coeur (Box 44)
        - S. Anne's (Box 44)
        - S. Etienne Du Mont (Box 45)
        - S. Eustache (Box 45)
        - S. Garmain De Pres (Box 45)
        - S. Gervais et S. Protais (Box 45)
        - S. Marguerite (Box 45)
        - S. Philippe Du Roule (Box 45)
        - S. Rouche (Box 45)
        - S. Sulpice (Box 45)
          - Exterior (Box 45)
          - Interior (Box 45)
        - Sorbonne Church (Box 45)
        - Val-de-Grace (Box 45)
      - Clubs (Box 45)
        - Hall of the Merchant Drapers (Box 45)
      - Fountain (Box 45)
        - Innocents (Box 45)
        - Fountain in Place De La Concorde (Box 45)
      - Gates (Box 45)
        - Porte S. Antoine (Box 45)
        - Port S. Denis (Box 46)
        - Porte S. M artin (Box 46)
      - Government Buildings (Box 46)
        - Barrieres (Box 46)
          - Hotel de Ville (Box 46)
          - Mint (Hotel Des Monnoies) (Box 46)
          - Palais du Justice (Box 46)
      - Hospitals (Box 46)
        - De La Charite (Box 46)
        - Hotel Dieu (Box 46)
        - Saint-Louis (Box 46)
        - La Salpetriere (Box 46)
      - Hotels (Box 46)
        - Various (Box 47)
        - Hotel D'Amelot (Box 47)
        - Hotel D'Aumont (Box 47)
        - Hotel de Baron Roger (Box 47)
        - Hotel de Batave Court (Box 47)
        - Hotel de Beauharnais (Box 47)
        - Hotel de Beauvais (Box 47)
        - Hotel De Biron (De Moras) (Box 47)
        - Hotel De Botterel (Box 47)
        - Hotel De Bovillon (Box 47)
        - Hotel De Borubon Conde (Box 47)
        - Hotel De Brunoy (Box 47)
        - Hotel Carnavalet (Box 47)
        - Hotel Chalon et Luxembourg (Box 47)
        - Hotel Chatelet (Box 47)
        - Hotel Cluny (Box 47)
        - Hotel Colvert (Box 47)
        - Hotel D'Estrees (Box 47)
        - Hotel D'Evreux (Box 47)
        - Hotel Fieubet (Box 47)
        - Hotel De Fermers (Box 47)
        - Hotel Gert or Du Jars (Box 47)
        - Hotel Guimard (Box 48)
        - Hotel Hollane (Box 48)
        - Hotel Invalides (Box 48)
          - Plans & Sections (Box 48)
          - Exterior (Box 48)
          - Interior (Box 48)
        - Hotel Lambert de Thorigny (Box 48)
        - Hotel Lamoignon (Box 48)
        - Hotel Lassay (Box 48)
        - Hotel Lauzun (Box 48)
        - Hotel Lionne (Box 48)
        - Hotel Lorge (Box 48)
        - Hotel Maine (Box 48)
        - Hotel Marmont (Box 48)
        - Hotel Monceaux (Box 48)
        - Hotel Noailles (Box 48)
        - Hotel Ritz (Box 48)
        - Hotel Rochechouart (Box 48)
        - Hotel Roquelaure (Box 48)
        - Hotel Rohan (Box 48)
        - Hotel de Salm (Box 49)
        - Hotel de Soubise, Palais des Archives (Box 49)
          - Plans (Box 49)
          - Exterior (Box 49)
          - Interior (Box 49)
          - Oval Salons (Box 49)
        - Hotel Sully (Box 49)
        - Hotel Thorigny (Box 49)
        - Hotel Toulouse or De La Vrillier (Box 49)
        - Hotel Villermare-Bourvallais (Box 49)
      - Houses (Box 49)
        - Various (Box 49)
        - House of Francis I (Box 49)
        - House of J.H. Mansart (Box 49)
        - Maison Du Dragon (Box 49)
      - Libraries (Box 49)
        - Bibliotheque De L'Arsenal (Box 49)
      - Museums (Box 49)
        - Louvre (Box 49)
          - Plans (Box 50)
          - Elevations (Box 50)
          - Historic Views (Box 50)
          - Air Views (Box 50)
          - Exterior (Box 50)
            - East Front (Box 50)
            - Seine (South) Side (Box 50)
            - Pettit Gallerie (Box 50)
          - Court (Box 50)
            - East Side (Box 50)
            - West Side (Box 50)
          - Interior (Box 50)
            - Gallerie D'Apollo (Box 50)
            - Salle Des Carlatides or Des Gardes (Box 50)
      - Palaces (Box 50)
        - Luxembourg (Box 50)
          - Exterior (Box 51)
          - Interior (Box 51)
        - Palais Royal (Box 51)
        - Lea Tuileries (Box 51)
          - Drawings & Plans (Box 51)
          - Exterior (Box 51)
          - Gardens (Box 51)
      - Parks (Box 51)
        - Beaugeon Garden (Box 51)
        - Parc Monceau (Box 51)
      - Schools (Box 51)
        - College of S. Cosmas (Box 51)
        - Beaux Art (Box 51)
        - Ecole De Droit (Box 51)
        - Ecole De Medecine (Box 51)
        - L'Institute or College de Qautre (Box 51)
        - Ecole Militaire (Box 51)
        - Sorbone (Box 51)
      - Squares (Box 51)
        - Concorde (Box 51)
        - Dauphine (Box 52)
        - Place Des Provin or The France (Box 52)
        - Place Vendome (Box 52)
        - Place Des Victoires (Box 52)
        - Vosges-Royal (Box 52)
      - Theaters (Box 52)
        - L O'Deon (Box 52)
        - Theater Francais (Box 52)
    - Passy (Box 52)
    - Pau (Box 52)
      - Chateau (Box 52)
    - Pavellon De Montreaul (Box 52)
    - Port Royal (Box 52)
    - Raincy (Box 52)
    - Rambouillet (Box 52)
    - Reims (Box 52)
    - Rennes (Box 52)
      - Hotel De Ville (Box 52)
      - Palais De Justice (Box 52)
    - Retz (Box 52)
    - Richelieu (Box 52)
    - Rodez (Box 52)
    - Rouen (Box 52)
      - La Madelaine (Box 52)
        - Gates (Box 52)
          - Gate of the William the Lion (Box 52)
        - Government Buildings (Box 53)
          - Hotel Ville (Box 53)
        - Houses (Box 53)
        - Squares (Box 53)
    - Saint Cloud (Box 53)
    - S. Denis (Box 53)
    - S. Germain-en-Lay (Box 53)
      - Chateau (Box 53)
        - Exterior (Box 53)
      - Hotel De Noailes (Box 53)
      - La Muette (Box 53)
      - Maison Du Val (Box 53)
    - St. Maur-Ler-Fosses (Box 53)
    - St. Remy (Box 53)
    - St. Sepulcre (Box 53)
    - St. Thegonnec (Box 53)
    - St. Wandrille (Box 53)
    - Saumur (Box 53)
    - Saverne (Box 53)
    - Sceaux (Box 53)
    - Sens (Box 53)
    - Sizun (Box 53)
    - Tarascon (Box 53)
    - Tillieres (Box 53)
    - Tocqville (Box 53)
    - Touche-Treby (Box 53)
    - Toulouse (Box 53)
      - Hotel D'Assezat (Box 53)
      - Hotel Bernuy (Box 53)
      - Hotel Laborde (Box 54)
    - Turny (Box 54)
    - Usse (Box 54)
    - Usson (Box 54)
    - Valencay (Box 54)
    - Vallery (Box 54)
    - Vaux-le-Vicomte (Box 54)
      - Chateau (Box 54)
        - Exterior (Box 54)
        - Interior (Box 54)
        - Park & Fountains (Box 54)
    - Verger (Box 54)
    - Versailles (Box 54)
      - Palace (Box 54)
        - Plan, Elevations & Sections (Box 54)
        - Air Views (Box 54–55)
        - Exterior (Box 55)
          - Paris Façade (East) (Box 55)
          - Garden Façade (West) (Box 55)
        - Gardens, Parks, Fountains (Box 55–56)
          - Orangerie (Box 56)
        - Interior (Box 56)
          - Bedroom of Louis XIV (Box 56)
          - Cabinet of Louis XV (Box 56)
          - Council Room of Louis XV (Box 56)
          - Galerie des Glaces (Hall of Mirrors) (Box 56)
          - Gallery of the Battles (Box 56)
          - King's Antechamber (Box 56)
          - Opera House (Box 56)
          - Queen's Antechamber (Box 56)
          - Queen's Chamber (Box 56)
          - Salon De La Guerre (Box 56)
          - Salon De Mans (Box 56)
          - Salon De Pendules (Box 56)
          - Salon of Queen Guards (Box 56)
          - Salon de Venus (Box 56)
          - Staircases (Box 56)
          - Chapel (Box 56)
            - Exterior (Box 56–57)
            - Interior (Box 57)
          - Grand Trianon (Box 57)
            - Exterior (Box 57)
            - Interior (Box 57)
          - Petit Trianon (Box 57)
            - Plans (Box 57)
            - Exterior (Box 57)
            - Interior (Box 57)
          - Hameau (Box 57)
          - Trianon the Celaine (Box 57)
          - Trianon Sous Bois (Box 57)
          - Pavillon Des Concerts (Box 57)
    - Villandry (Box 57)
    - Villarceaus (Box 57)
      - Chateau (Box 57)
        - Exterior (Box 58)
    - Villers-Cotterets (Box 58)
    - Vicennes (Box 58)
    - Vonne (Box 58)
- Germany (Box 58)
  - General (Box 58)
  - Architects (Box 58)
    - Bosboom, Simon (Box 58)
    - Decker, Paul (Box 58)
    - Durer, Albrecht, 1471-1525 (Box 58)
    - Gattinara (Box 58)
    - Gilly, Friedrich (Box 58)
    - Nizza & Erwsiterung (Box 58)
    - Popehman (Box 58)
    - Schluter, Andreas (Box 58)
    - Speckle (Box 58)
  - Cities (Box 58)
    - Andechus (Box 58)
    - Augsburg (Box 58)
    - Ascaffenburg (Box 58)
    - Bamberg (Box 58)
    - Banz (Box 58)
      - Exterior (Box 58)
      - Interior (Box 58)
    - Bayreuth (Box 58)
    - Benrath (Box 58)
    - Berg-am-Laim (Box 58)
    - Berlin (Box 58)
      - Arsenal (Box 58)
      - Castle (Box 59)
      - Brandenburg Gate (Box 59)
      - Opera House (Box 59)
      - Schloss Charlottenburg (Box 59)
    - Birnau (Box 59)
    - Braunschweig (Box 59)
    - Bremen (Box 59)
      - Rathaus (Box 59)
      - Schutting (Box 59)
    - Bruchsal (Box 59)
      - Bishop's Palace (Box 59)
        - Exterior (Box 59)
        - Interior (Box 59)
    - Cassel (Box 59)
    - Charlottenburg (Box 59)
    - Coburg (Box 60)
    - Cologne (Box 60)
    - Cothen in Anhalt (Box 60)
    - Danzig (Box 60)
    - Dillingen (Box 60)
    - Diessen (Box 60)
    - Dresden (Box 60)
      - Frauenkirche (Box 60)
      - Hofkirche (Box 60)
      - Zwinger (Box 60)
        - Plans & Drawings (Box 60)
        - General Views (Box 60)
        - Exterior (Box 60)
        - Pavillions (Box 60)
        - Fountains (Box 60)
    - Einsielden (Box 60)
    - Ellwangen (Box 60)
    - Erbach (Box 60)
    - Ettal (Box 60)
    - Etwashausen (Box 60)
    - Falkenhust (Box 60)
    - Frankfurt (Box 61)
    - Freiburg (Box 61)
    - Freystadt (Box 61)
    - Fulda (Box 61)
    - Furstenfeldbruck (Box 61)
    - Grussau (Box 61)
    - Guenzburg (Box 61)
    - Halbertstadt (Box 61)
    - Halmeln (Box 61)
    - Hannover (Box 61)
    - Heidelberg (Box 61)
      - Castle (Box 61)
    - Herrenchiemsee (Box 61)
    - Hildescheim (Box 61)
    - Ingolstadt (Box 61)
    - Kappel (Box 61)
    - Karlsruhe (Box 61)
    - Kempten (Box 61)
    - Kloster Lechfeld (Box 61)
    - Koblenz (Box 61)
    - Landsberg (Box 61)
    - Lemgo (Box 61)
    - Lubreck (Box 61)
      - Rathaus (Box 61)
    - Ludwigsburg (Box 61)
      - Castle (Box 61)
        - Plans (Box 61)
        - Exterior (Box 61)
        - Interior (Box 61)
    - Ludwigslust (Box 61)
    - Mainz (Box 61)
    - Manheim (Box 62)
    - Mon Pepos (Box 62)
    - Munich (Box 62)
      - Churches (Box 62)
        - Oreifaltigkeitskirche (Box 62)
        - Heiliggeistkirche (Box 62)
        - S. Anna-Am-Lehel (Box 62)
        - S. Michael (Box 62)
        - Theatiner Church (Box 62)
        - S. John Nepomuk (Box 62)
      - Palaces (Box 62)
        - Residenz (Box 62)
        - Royal Palace (Box 62)
    - Munster (Box 62)
    - Neresheim (Box 62)
      - Abbey Church (Box 62)
        - Plans (Box 62)
        - Exterior (Box 62)
        - Interior (Box 62)
    - Nurnburg (Box 62)
    - Nymphenberg (Box 62)
      - Schools (Box 62)
        - Exterior (Box 62–63)
        - Interior (Box 63)
      - Amalienburg (Box 63)
      - Banderburg (Box 63)
      - Magdelene Klause (Box 63)
      - Pagodenburg (Box 63)
    - Obermarchtal (Box 63)
    - Osterhofen (Box 63)
    - Ottobeuren (Box 63)
      - Plans (Box 63)
      - Exterior (Box 63)
      - Interior (Box 63)
        - Altar (Box 63)
        - Vaults (Box 63)
        - Library (Box 63)
    - Pommersfelden (Box 63)
      - Plans & Sections (Box 63)
      - Engravings (Box 63)
      - Exterior (Box 64)
        - Stables (Box 64)
      - Interior (Box 64)
        - Stairway (Box 64)
    - Posen (Box 64)
    - Potsdam (Box 64)
      - Stadtschloss (City Palace) (Box 64)
        - Exterior (Box 64)
        - Interior (Box 64)
      - New Palace (Box 64)
      - Sans Souci Palace (Box 64)
        - Exterior (Box 64)
        - Interior (Box 64–65)
      - Communs (Box 65)
      - Park and Garden Buildings (Box 65)
        - Chinese Pavillion (Box 65)
    - Richenau (Box 65)
    - Rheinsberg (Box 65)
    - Rohr (Box 65)
    - Rothenburg (Box 65)
    - Rot an der Rot (Box 65)
    - Rott-am-Inn (Box 65)
    - Saarbrucken (Box 65)
    - Schaftlarn (Box 65)
    - Schleissheim (Box 65)
    - Schussenried (Box 65)
    - Schwetzingen (Box 65)
    - Solitude (Box 65)
    - S. Blasien (Box 65)
    - Steingaden (Box 65)
    - Steinhausen (Box 65)
      - Pilgrimage Church (Box 65)
    - Stuttgart (Box 65)
    - Ulm (Box 66)
    - Tegernsee (Box 66)
    - Vierzehnheiligen (Box 66)
      - Models & Plans (Box 66)
      - Exterior (Box 66)
      - Interior (Box 66)
        - Altars (Box 66)
        - Sculpture detail (Box 66)
    - Waldsassen (Box 66)
    - Weingarten (Box 66)
      - Plans (Box 66)
      - Exterior (Box 66)
      - Interior (Box 66)
    - Weltenburg (Box 66)
      - Exterior (Box 66)
      - Interior (Box 66)
    - Westerndorf (Box 66)
    - Wiblingen (Box 67)
      - Plans & Sections (Box 67)
      - Interior (Box 67)
    - Wies (Box 67)
    - Wilhelmshorl (Box 67)
    - Wolfenbuttel (Box 67)
    - Wurzburg (Box 67)
      - Castle (Residenz) (Box 67)
        - Plans & Drawings (Box 67)
        - Exterior (Box 67)
        - Interior (Box 67)
      - Court Church or Castle Chapel (Box 67)
      - Cathedral (Box 68)
      - Neumunster Church (Box 68)
      - Schonborn Chapel (Box 68)
    - Zwiefalten (Box 68)
      - Abbey Church (Box 68)
        - Exterior (Box 68)
      - Interior (Box 68)
- Holland (Box 68)
  - Various (Box 68)
  - Architects (Box 68)
    - Vries, Hans Vredam da (Box 68)
  - Cities (Box 68)
    - Amsterdam (Box 68)
      - General: Plans & Air Views (Box 68)
      - Sphardic Synagogue (Box 68)
      - Town Hall (Box 68)
        - Exterior (Box 68)
        - Interior (Box 68)
        - Exterior Sculpture (Box 68)
        - Interior Sculpture (Box 68)
        - Churches (Box 68)
        - Houses (Box 68)
        - Palaces (Box 68)
  - Delft (Box 68)
  - Haarlem (Box 68)
  - The Hague (Box 68)
  - Heemstede (Box 68)
  - Hoorn (Box 68)
  - Middachten (Box 68)
  - Rotterdam (Box 68)
  - Utrecht (Box 68)
- Hungary (Box 68)
  - Bartfa (Box 68)
  - Budapest (Box 68)
  - Esztergom (Box 68)
  - Rackeve (Box 68)
  - Visegrad (Box 68)
- Italy (Box 68)
  - General (Box 68–69)
  - Unknown Houses in the Country (Box 69)
    - Ornaments (Box 69)
    - Plans (Box 69)
  - Architects (Box 69)
    - Alberti, L.B. (Box 69)
    - Bernini (Box 69)
      - Louvre Projects (Box 69)
      - Design for Opera Sant'Alessio (Box 69)
    - Bibiena family (Box 69)
    - Bibiena Ferdinando (Box 69)
    - Bibiena, Francesco (Box 69)
    - Bibiena, Giuseppe Galli (Box 69)
    - Borromini (Box 70)
    - Bramante (Box 70)
    - Brunelleschi (Box 70)
    - Buontalenti (Box 70)
    - Cataneo, Pietro (Box 70)
    - Cesariano (Box 70)
    - Dosio, Giovanni Antonio, 1533- (Box 70)
    - Filarete (Box 70)
      - Plusiapolis I & II (Box 70)
      - From Treatise on Architecture (Box 70–71)
    - Fontana, Carlo (Box 71)
    - Fontana, Domenico (Box 71)
    - Francesco di Giorgio, Martini, 1439-1502 (Box 71)
    - Ghiberti, Buonaccorso, 1451-1516 (Box 71)
    - Giacondo, Fra (Box 71)
    - Giovanni Di Bologna (Giambolo) (Box 71)
    - Guarini, Guarino (Box 71)
    - Juvara, Filippo (Box 71)
    - Labacco, Antonio (Box 71)
    - Leonardo da Vinci (Box 71–72)
    - Maderna (Box 72)
    - Michelangelo (Box 72)
      - Fotification Drawings (Box 72)
    - Michelozzo di Bartolomeo (Box 72)
    - Michelle (Box 72)
    - Palladio, Andrea (Box 72–73)
    - Peruzzi, Balda (Box 73)
    - Piranesi, G.B. (Box 73)
    - Quarenchi, Giacomo (Box 73)
    - San Gallo, Antonio the elder (Box 73)
    - San Gallo, Antonio the Younger (Box 73)
    - San Gallo, Francisco (Box 73)
    - San Gallo, Guiliano (Box 73)
    - Scamozzi, Vicenzo (Box 73)
    - Sansovino, Jacopo (Box 73)
    - Serlio, Sebastiano (Box 73–74)
    - Silvani, Gherardo, 1589-1675 (Box 74)
    - Sperandio (Box 74)
    - Vasari, Giorgio (Box 74)
    - Vignola, Giacomo (Box 74)
  - Cities (Box 74)
    - Abbiategrasso (Box 74)
    - Ancona (Box 74)
    - Antella (Box 74)
    - Aosta (Box 74)
    - Aquila (Box 74)
    - Arezzo (Box 74)
      - Churches (Box 74)
        - Badia (Box 74)
        - S. Annunziata (Box 74)
        - S. Maria Dell Grazie (Box 74)
    - Ariccia (Box 74)
    - Artimino (Box 74)
    - Bagnaia (Box 74)
      - Villa Lante (Box 74)
    - Bagnolo (Box 74–75)
    - Bassano (Box 75)
    - Bergamo (Box 75)
    - Bologna (Box 75)
      - Churches (Box 75)
        - Di Corpus Domini (Box 75)
        - Madonna Di Galleria (Box 75)
        - S. Domenico (Box 75)
        - S. Maria della Vita (Box 75)
        - S. Michelle in Basco (Box 75)
        - S. Petronio (Box 75)
        - S. Pietro (Box 75)
        - Spirito Santo (Box 75)
      - Palaces (Box 75)
        - Albergati (Box 75)
        - Bargellini (now Davia) (Box 75)
        - Bevilaqua (Box 75)
        - Bocchi (Box 75)
        - Bolognini (Box 75)
        - Fantuzzi (Cloetta) (Box 75)
        - Farnese (Box 75)
        - Del Podesta (Box 75)
        - Salem (Malvezzi Campecgi) (Box 75)
      - Schools (Box 75)
      - Villas (Box 75)
    - Bomarzo (Box 75)
    - Bra (Box 75)
    - Brescia (Box 75)
      - Churches (Box 75)
      - Gates (Box 75)
    - Caffagiuolo (Box 75)
    - Caldogno (Box 75)
    - Campiglia (Box 75)
    - Capranica (Box 75)
    - Caprarola (Box 75)
      - Palazzo Farnese (Box 75)
        - Plans (Box 75)
        - Exterior (Box 76)
        - Interior (Box 76)
        - Gardens: Palazzina (Box 76)
    - Careggi (Box 76)
    - Carignano (Box 76)
    - Carpi (Box 76)
    - Caserta (Box 76)
      - Palazzo Reale (Box 76)
        - Plans, Sections (Box 76)
        - Exterior (Box 76)
        - Gardens (Box 76)
        - Interior (Box 76)
  - Castello (Box 76)
  - Castiglione D'Olona (Box 76)
  - Castiglione Fiorentino (Box 76)
  - Citta di Castello (Box 76)
  - Civitta Di Castello (Box 76)
  - Civitta Vecchia (Box 76)
  - Colle Di Val D'Elsa (Box 76)
  - Como (Box 76)
    - Churches (Box 76)
      - Cathedral (Box 76)
  - Cortona (Box 76)
    - Churches (Box 76)
      - S. Maria del Calcinato (Box 76)
        - Exterior (Box 76)
        - Interior (Box 76–77)
      - S. Maria Nuova (Box 77)
  - Crema (Box 77)
  - Cremona (Box 77)
  - Faenza (Box 77)
  - Fanzolo (Box 77)
  - Ferrara (Box 77)
  - Fiesole (Box 77)
    - Churches (Box 77)
      - Badia (Box 77)
  - Finale (Box 77)
    - Villas (Box 77)
      - Villa de Medici (Box 77)
  - Florence (Box 77)
    - General (Box 77)
      - Maps and Plans (Box 77)
      - Views (Box 77)
    - Arches (Box 77)
    - Bridges (Box 77)
      - Ponte S. Trinita (Box 77)
      - Ponte Vecchio (Box 77)
    - Churches (Box 77)
      - Cathedral (Box 77)
        - Dome (Box 78)
          - Plans & Sections (Box 78)
          - Exterior (Box 78)
          - Interior (Box 78)
        - Lantern (Box 78)
      - Church of the Ognissanti (Box 78)
      - SS. Annunziata (Box 78)
      - SS. Apostoli (Box 78)
      - S. Croce (Box 78)
      - Pazzi Chapel (Box 78)
        - Plans (Box 78)
        - Exterior (Box 78)
        - Interior (Box 78)
        - Dome (Box 78)
      - S. Felicita (Box 78)
      - S. Francisco al Monte (Box 79)
      - S. Gaetano (Box 79)
      - S. Giovannino (Box 79)
      - S. Lorenzo (Box 79)
        - Plans and Sections (Box 79)
        - Façade Designs (Box 79)
        - Exterior (Box 79)
        - Interior (Box 79)
          - Chapel of the Princes (Box 79)
          - New Sacristy (Medici Chapel) (Box 79)
            - Exterior (Box 79)
            - Interior (Box 79)
          - Old Sacristy (Box 79)
          - Laurentian Library (Box 80)
            - Michelangelo drawings (Box 80)
            - Plans & Sections (Box 80)
            - Vestibule & Staircase (Box 80)
            - Reading Hall (Box 80)
      - S. Marco (Box 80)
      - S. Maria degli Angeli (Box 80)
      - S. Maria del Carmine (Box 80)
      - S. Maria Maddalena Dei Pazzi (Box 80)
      - S. Maria Novella (Box 80)
        - Façade (Box 80)
        - Façade details & Doors (Box 80)
        - Chapels (Box 80)
      - S. Miniato al Monte: Chapel of the Cardinal of Portugal (Box 80)
      - S. Pancrazio (Box 80)
      - S. Spirito (Box 81)
        - Exterior (Box 81)
        - Interior (Box 81)
      - Sacristy (Box 81)
      - S. Stefano (Box 81)
      - S. Trinita (Box 81)
    - Fountains (Box 81)
    - Gates (Box 81)
    - Hospitals (Box 81)
      - Hospital of the Innocent (Box 81)
        - Exterior (Box 81)
        - Interior (Box 81)
        - Cloisters (Box 82)
    - Houses (Box 82)
    - Loggia (Box 82)
      - Loggia dei Mercato Nuovo (Box 82)
      - Loggia Di S. Paolo (Box 82)
    - Palaces (Box 82)
      - Various (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Antinori (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Bartolini (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Bourtourlin (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Corsi (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Davanzati (Box 82)
        - Exterior (Box 82)
        - Interior (Box 82)
        - Courtyard (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Durazzo-Pallavicini (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Fenzi (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Gondi (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Guadagni (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Larderel (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Manelli-Riccardi (Box 82)
      - Palazzo Medici-Riccardi (Box 82)
        - Exterior (Box 83)
        - Interior (Box 83)
        - Courtyard (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Montalvi (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Nonfinito (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Pandolfini (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Di Parte Cuelfa (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Pazzi-Quaratesi (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Pitti (Box 83)
        - Exterior (Box 83)
        - Interior (Box 83)
        - Courtyard (Box 83)
        - Boboli Garderns (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Rucelli (Box 83)
      - Palazzo Strozzi (Box 84)
        - Exterior (Box 84)
        - Interior (Box 84)
      - Palazzo Torregiani (Box 84)
      - Palazzo Uffizi (Box 84)
      - Palazzo Ugoccione (Box 84)
      - Palazzo Vecchio (Box 84)
        - Exterior (Box 84)
          - Court (Box 84)
        - Interior (Box 84)
          - Hall (Box 84)
    - Squares (Box 84)
    - Villas (Box 84)
      - Villa Curiona (Box 84)
      - Villa Demidoff at Pratolino (Box 84)
      - Villa Reale Di Pretava (Box 84)
      - Villa Salvati (Box 84)
  - Faino Della Chiano (Box 84)
  - Frascati (Box 84)
    - Churches (Box 84)
    - Villas (Box 84)
      - Villa Aldobrandini (Box 84–85)
      - Villa Conti (Box 85)
      - Villa Falconieri (Box 85)
      - Villa Mondragone (Box 85)
      - Villa Picolomini (Box 85)
      - Villa Taverna Borghese (Box 85)
      - Villa Torlonia (Box 85)
  - Galluzzo (Box 85)
  - Genoa (Box 85)
    - Churches (Box 85)
      - SS. Annunziata (Box 85)
      - S. Maria (Box 85)
      - S. Maria Carignano (Box 85)
      - S. Siro (Box 85)
    - Palaces (Box 85)
      - Dege' Imperiali (Box 85)
      - Palazzo Doria-Tursi (Box 85)
      - Palazzo Durazzo (Box 85)
      - Palazzo Negrone (Box 85)
      - Palazzo Parodi (Box 85)
    - Schools (Box 85)
      - University (Box 85)
      - Pal. Dell' Universita (Box 85)
    - Squares (Box 85)
    - Theaters (Box 85)
  - Genzano (Box 85)
  - Gubbio (Box 85)
  - Imola (Box 86)
  - Impruneta (Box 86)